shoutwire.com 2019-01-04

# Privacy Policy | Shoutwire

##  Overall privacy statement 

We take your privacy seriously. Because we gather certain types of information about our users we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. These privacy practices apply to the Web site that you were viewing when you clicked through to this policy, which is operated by us directly, our partner, or our affiliate. 

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. 

We collect personally identifiable information when you provide it to us, such as when you register on one of our sites, when you subscribe to an e-mail newsletter or when you register to use certain services. Several of the services that we offer on our sites, may require registration as a condition of use. Once you register you are no longer anonymous to us. We may also receive information about you from other sources and add it to the information you provided to us. 

Your Internet browser has a feature called "cookies" which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of our sites. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit our sites, although active participation in certain areas of our sites may require cookies. Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information when, in which case we use the information to enhance your services. You may elect not to allow cookies to be collected by adjusting your settings on your browser. 

We also automatically receive and record information from our servers and from your browser, including your IP address, the time of your visit to pages on our site, and information about pages you visited. Unless you have registered for one of our products or services, the information we gather through the use of tracking technologies cannot be matched with any personally identifiable information about you unless you have specifically given us personally identifiable information, in which case we use the information to enhance your services. 

We will make your personally identifiable information available to other companies or people when: 

  * We have your consent to share the information 
  * We have engaged companies to work with us or on our behalf to provide a product or service that you have requested 
  * You use co-branded services. When you use a co-branded service within our network of sites you grant us permission to pass your registration information back to that service partner. Their use of your information is subject to their applicable privacy policies. 
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process; or we believe that your actions violate applicable laws, shoutwire.com [Terms of Service](http://www.shoutwire.com/terms-of-service.php) or any usage guidelines for specific products or services, or threaten the rights, property, or safety of our company, our users, or others 

You can correct or change the information collected during registration for any of our sites. The instructions for doing this can be found in our member services areas. Users may change information at any time and as often as necessary. Currently, we do not offer users a means by which to completely delete personal information established at the time of registration. 

Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected first within this area of our network of Web sites.
